export const circle_of_fifths = {
    cards: [
        {
			front: "C",
			back: "F"
		},
        {
			front: "F",
			back: "B♭"
		},
        {
			front: "B♭",
			back: "E♭"
		},
        {
			front: "A♭",
			back: "D♭/C♯"
		},
        {
			front: "D♭/C♯",
			back: "F♯/G♭"
		},
        {
			front: "F♯/G♭",
			back: "B/C♭"
		},
        {
			front: "B/C♭",
			back: "E"
		},
        {
			front: "E",
			back: "A"
		},
        {
			front: "A",
			back: "D"
		},
        {
			front: "D",
			back: "G"
		},
        {
			front: "G",
			back: "C"
		}
    ]
}

export const circle_of_fourths = {
    cards: [
        {
			front: "F",
			back: "C"
		},
        {
			front: "B♭",
			back: "F"
		},
        {
			front: "E♭",
			back: "B♭"
		},
        {
			front: "D♭/C♯",
			back: "A♭"
		},
        {
			front: "F♯/G♭",
			back: "D♭/C♯"
		},
        {
			front: "B/C♭",
			back: "F♯/G♭"
		},
        {
			front: "E",
			back: "B/C♭"
		},
        {
			front: "A",
			back: "E"
		},
        {
			front: "D",
			back: "A"
		},
        {
			front: "G",
			back: "D"
		},
        {
			front: "C",
			back: "G"
		}  
    ]
}